

□ (+1) 647-999-1210 | Maminn.lee@mail.utoronto.ca | Maminnlee.github.io | Onaminthecoder |

Software Engineer with passions in developing scalable software solutions

Summary _

Current 4th year Computer Science student at University of Toronto. 4+ years at University of Toronto specializing in Computer System and Web Application. Previously a Freelance Web Developer for Korea University and a Junior Developer at start-up company BluRoot. Super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and Racket. Interested in optimizing everything, and learning new technologies when the opportunity arises.

Education

University of Toronto - St. George

Toronto, Canada

H.B.Sc. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND STATISTICS

Expected Graduation June 2021

• Specialized in Computer Science with Focus in Computer Systems and Web Applications

Work Experience

Korea University Toronto, Canada (Freelance)

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

Nov 2019 - Jan 2020

- Responsible for building a website for Physics department used by 1000+ students.
- Defined and managed development and QA processes using Git and Selenium.
- Increased web traffic by 29% from previous year.

BluRoot Toronto, Canada

JUNIOR DEVELOPER (CONTRACT)

May 2019 - July 2019

- Increased company-wide productivity by 11% by defining development processes using Git Issue board.
- Developed front-end solutions using React and back-end solutions using Node.js for clients.
- · Leveraged knowledge in JavaScript, Back-end, CRM

Skills

LANGUAGE: C, PYTHON, JAVA, JAVASCRIPT, BASH, SHELL SCRIPT, SWIFT, RACKET

FRAMEWORK: ANGULAR, REACT, DJANGO, SELENIUM

OTHER: LINUX, SYSTEMS PROGRAMMING, FUNCTIONAL PROGRAMMING, AI/MACHINE LEARNING

Projects.

COVID-19 Live Monitor

ANGULAR, HTML/CSS, DevOps

May 2020

- · Asynchronously fetched live COVID-19 data from a live API and displayed it on beautiful UIs using Angular.
- https://covid-19-monitor.netlify.app/

Sorting Visualizer

Algorithms, React, Redux

Jul. 2020

• Built React / Redux application for visualizing sorting algorithms. Implemented Merge Sort, Quick Sort, Heap Sort, and Bubble Sort.

Mini-mini (iOS) app

SWIFT, XCODE, GAME DESIGN

Aug. 2020 - current

• Created multiple mini games using Swift and Xcode. Extensive use of functional programming.

Tech Up - (E-commerce website)

E-COMMERCE, DJANGO, HTML/CSS Feb. 2020

· Implemented an E-Commerce website from model design to deployment to sell phone related products.

Hamin Lee · Résumé